(Raj:)it's the guy who
shows me YouTube videos
(Raj:)of people getting hit
in the nuts.
(Howard:)You're crazy.
(Howard:)I've worked with Hawking.
He's got a great sense of humor.
(Howard:)And I think he'd like it.
(Bernadette:)Okay, call him and show him.
(Bernadette:)I dare you.
(Howard:)I have no problem calling him.
(Bernadette:)Fine, then do it.
(Howard:)Fine, I will.
(Bernadette:)While you're bothering the
world's most famous scientist,
(Bernadette:)be sure to show him
how funny he looks
(Bernadette:)getting stuck
under our dishwasher.
(Raj:)What's this button do?
(Remote-control Hawking:)Gentlemen,
start your wheelchairs.
(Howard:)You laughed when that guy
got hit in the nuts.
(Raj:)I laughed because
the guy was Leonard.
(Sheldon:)I admire you, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Really, why?
(Sheldon:)You're happy with who you are.
(Sheldon:)You don't get jealous
of other people.